http://www.gallerym.com/pages/privacy

Andy Warhol+
More...
Howard Schatz+
More...
This is the Web site of GALLERY M
Our postal address is GALLERY M180 Cook St, Suite 101Denver, CO, 80206
We can be reached via our online request form.
Or you can reach us by telephone at 303.331.8400
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).
We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.
The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending email to us at the above address and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our company.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.You may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending email to us at the above address.
Please provide us with your exact name and address.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. They also may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending email to us at the above address or calling us at the above telephone number. Simply provide us with your correct phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.
Amended May 24, 2018: General Data Protection Regulation
Persons who are based in the European Union can further control their contact with our online services and websites.   To update your preferences for MARKETING by email, phone and direct mail, use our Update Marketing Profile link here.  For all other inquiries reach a representative via our online update form.
All users of GALLERY M company services have select rights through our company.
Your Right to Control and Access Your Information
You have control over your personal information and how it is collected, used, and shared. For example, you have a right to:
Change or correct personal data. You can edit any personal data with us by reaching us through our online update form.
Access and take your data. You can also ask us for a copy of personal data you provided to us.  We will get back to you within 30 days.
Ask us to stop using or limit our use of your personal data in certain circumstances—for example, if we have no lawful basis to keep using your data, or if you think your personal data is inaccurate.
Object to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes. You can ask us to stop sending you marketing messages at any time.  This can be done through any email with an included Unsubscribe link.
Ask us to delete your data. You have a right to be forgotten and request your personal information on file be deleted by contacting us.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes to this privacy statement on http://gallerym.com/ and other places we deem appropriate so you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of the site after such changes have been posted indicates your consent and acceptance of such changes.
Effective Date
This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on May 24, 2018.
"Best of Denver 2000" award for Jazz Photographer Ted Williams
GALLERY M official 2002 Winter Olympics gallery for Clemens Briels in Front Range
March 2003:
GALLERY M welcomes its 1000th collector to the GALLERY M art network
October 2005:
Peter Max introduces over 80 original works at GALLERY M.
October 2007:
Howard Schatz selects GALLERY M for H2O world release.
November 2009:
Host of the Stan Brakhage Vision Award Reception with Denver Intl. Film Festival
January 2019:
Exhibited in over 17 internationally recognized fairs, including Art Aspen, Art Hamptons, Market Art & Design, and Art Southampton
to add multiple items to your quote, please fill qty field then click on "add to quote"
more details
close
